Md. Khasrur Rahman

Full Stack Developer

Website: http://portfolio-ratin.com/

GitHub: github.com/KhasrurRahman

LinkedIn: /in/khasrur-rahmna



Mobile: +8801761955765
Email: Khasrur8@gmail.com

Address: Dhaka

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to express my interest in interviewing for the position of Web Application Developer. During my 3 years of experience as a full-stack Web Developer, I have developed both the functional and aesthetic components of client websites. I believe I can make an immediate impact on your organization with my unique blend of skills and passion.

My professional experience includes using programming languages such as PHP and JavaScript to create various features for client websites. I also have experience in developing and managing SQL databases. Combine this with my ability to thrive in a collaborative environment, and I think that makes me a perfect fit for Brick stone Digital. Here are some highlights of my accomplishments as a Developer:

- Now I am working on Trust Innovation Limited (Bangladesh Army) as a Full Stack Developer
- Still, 30-35 complex and dynamic web applications for different companies are running live. The application Documentation is done to me, which is stored in GITHUB.
- All the application which I have made are designed and database relation also made by me.
- Successfully collaborated and efficiently communicated with project stakeholders to bring their vision to digital reality
- Earned a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from Daffodil International University
- Wrote code for various website functions using PHP, LARAVEL (framework), JAVASCRIPT, AJAX, VUE JS
- Tested and troubleshot all Web functions to ensure the optimal user experience

My extensive knowledge of programming languages, Computer Science, and the principles Development make me equipped to accelerate Brick stone Digital's progress toward their goals. I look forward to discussing this position further in an interview.

Thank you for your consideration.

Sincerely,

Md. Khasrur Rahman

Md. Khasrur Rahman

Full Stack Developer

Website: portfolio-ratin.com

GitHub: github.com/KhasrurRahman

LinkedIn: in/khasrur-rahmna



Mobile: +8801761955765

Email: Khasrur8@gmail.com

Address: Dhaka, Bangladesh

About Me



I have 3.5 years of experience specializing in front end back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Having an in-depth knowledge including advanced HTML5, CSS, CSS3, PHP, LARAVEL, JAVASCRIPT, VUEJS, AJAX, jQuery, C, MySql, Advance sql query. Strong background in management and leadership.

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 PHP LARAVEL JAVASCRIPT WORDPRESS MYSQL VUE JS

MYSQL ADVANCE SQL QUERY VIDEO EDTING **SOFTWARE**

PHP STORM
WEB STROM
NETBINS
PYCHARM
SUBLINE TEXT
NAVICAT
WINSCP
JUPYTER

SONY VAGAS PRO MICROSOFT WORD

PUTTY

PERSONAL

COMMUNICATION PROBLEM SOLVING DEDICATION TEAMWORK CREATIVITY

EXPERIENCE



SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TRUST INNOVATION LIMITED (Bangladesh Army)

Dhaka, Bangladesh — OCT 2020-Present

Trust Innovation Limited (TIL), a sister concern of Bangladesh Army Welfare Trust, is a professional ICT solution provider and a valuable partner of Bangladesh Army.

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER, BD24REPORT

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Nov 2019-Oct 2020

bd24report.com is one of the most popular online News portals of Bangladesh updating 24/7 with breaking, political, business, entertainment, sports, lifestyle and crime news

LIVE PROJECTS

AUTOMATED INTERNET BILLING SOFTWARE (MIKROTIK+SMS+PAYMENT GATEWAY)

Frontend: https://resnet.tilbd.net/

Admin panel: https://internetbilling.mycartrackingpoint.com/login

Email: admin@gmail.com

Pass: admin123

subscriber panel: https://internetbilling.mycartrackingpoint.com/subscriber/login

Username: test-123 Pass: test-123

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Dec 2020-Mar 2020

Trust Innovation Limited is playing a major role in the cantonment area by providing better services especially for internet service delivery.

AUTOMATED GPS TRACKING AND BILLING SOFTWARE

Frontend: https://safetygpstracker.com.bd

Admin panel: https://gpsbilling.mycartrackingpoint.com/login

Phone: 01761955765

Pass: 123

•

customer panel: https://gpsbilling.mycartrackingpoint.com/user/user dashboard

Phone: 01761955769

Pass: 123456

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Jan 2020-Mar 2020

Safety GPS Tracker offer real time GPS Vehicle Tracking Solution. Our GPS Tracking Software enables you to track accurate location of your Fleet & Vehicles.

POS MANAGEMENT SOFTWARE

Link: http://erp.tashfiaexport.com/

Admin panel: http://pos.mycartrackingpoint.com/login

Phone: admin@gmail.com

Pass: til123

Dhaka, Bangladesh — nov 2021-jan 2022

WEB APPLICATION, BD CASE REFERENCE

Link: https://bdcasereference.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh — Sep 2019-nov 2019

Bd Case Reference is the first free online case reference in Bangladesh which helps to find specific case references or decisions of the Supreme Court of Bangladesh.

TRAINING COURSES

WEB DEVELOPMENT

leverage on Information and Communication Technologies (LICT) — NOV 2017-FEB 2018

Name: Frontend and Backend Development

Language: Php,javascript,mysql

Framework: Laravel

Batch: 19



WEB DESIGEN

Bangladesh Association of Software and Information Services (BASIS) — Jan 2017-Mar 2017

Name: Professional Web Design

Learning Item: Html,css,Bootstrap,Javascript

Batch: 61

GRAPHIC DESIGNE

MIST — Jan 2016-Mar 2016

Name: Professional Graphic Design

Software: Photoshop Cs6

Batch: 3

EDUCATION

B.SC. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

Daffodil International University — 2016-2020

Last 2 years CGPA: 3.78 Total CGPA:3.43

Passing Year: 2020



HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (HSC)

Satkhira govt college — 2015-2016

Result: A Board: Jessore Passing year: 2015

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (SSC)

Satkhira govt high school — 2013-2015

Result: A Board: Jessore Passing year: 2013



MEMBERSHIP

Programming club: Daffodil International University Computer & Programming Club Cultural Club: Daffodil International University Cultural Club

LANGUAGES



Bangla: native language

English: intermediate (speaking, reading); basic (writing)

REFERENCES



S M Nafiul Hossain, MPA(DU), MBA(DU) Bsc(KUET) Consultant ,UNDP Timor-Leste Former Lead Business Analyst-Bangladesh Army

Mobile: +8801833181361

Email: smnafiulhossain@gmail.com

SIGNATURE

(MD.Khasrur Rahman) Date: 11-01-2022

Patin